Friends with Brews! You act like you've never heard that every time you hear it
No, it's not. I'm moving to the music. I'm moving to the melodious music
There's no music because the melodious timber of your voice your dulcet tone is no music
There IS no paper jam because Peter
Nikolaidis hated everything that I came up with but did not make any effort whatsoever to find something that he could live with
Have you thought about having an AI generate our theme song?
No, but I'm sure you have.
Well now I did.
Okay, let's talk about our brews first because both my cup and my beer have been sitting here for a few minutes.
Well you go first then.
Well, I’m just having marryin' berries again.
This is the same one that I had like three episodes ago.
See like I go to great lengths to try to have a new beer every single time.
Peter almost all the time I do.
Very... I don't... in fact, I don't know if I ever have repeated myself. Maybe once before.
So it's okay to do that. I will confess that I do repeat the same coffee anytime
I have a decaf it's always the same decaf. Right, which I don't do. So far I have not
repeated coffees on this show. Fine be that way you and your trade coffee. Look
at that. Ooh, Powell's! Hey I was there you took me there. But look at the color yeah
we talked about that last time. It's marionberry colored. Uh-huh. People just
Just for—I should clarify, yes, I've had this before, but it is the Ex Novo Brewing
Marionberries, and it's a combination of—what is it a combination of, Peter?
It's a combination of Marionberries, raspberries, and it's also got some white wheat flaked
oats and mosaic, whatever the hell mosaic is.
It has mosaic.
I thought it was an old browser of some kind.
It was.
And most of our listeners—I don't know.
Do you think our listeners know what Mosaic is? Based on our survey, our tens of listeners,
would you think that people know what Mosaic was or don't know what Mosaic was?
They probably do because it's probably old people that listen to us and now I'm going
to get a lot of hate mail. Actually, I'm not going to get hate mail because I've never
given an email address to this. I'm going to get hate, Moose. Hate Mastodon. Hate Toot.
So here's an interesting thing. I'm looking on the website for Golden Road Brewing. Those
are the makers of two beers that I've had on this cast prior. One is the famous Mango
Cart, which was a thumbs up. And there was also Guava Cart. Well, I have a third beer
by them today, and I'm not able to find it on their website. They might have discontinued
Oh my god, what a surprise a beer company that has a website that doesn't have one of their beers anywhere on it
but i'm thinking that maybe they've discontinued this one because I did buy it last year and it was part of a
three flavor pack it had mango cart guava cart and
melon cart
Now I will say this out of all three. This one is the least distinctive least memorable
Not my favorite, but...
Okay, tell us what it is.
Tell us what this least favorite...
I am having the same.
...immemorable or unmemorable...
Well, it is a watermelon wheat ale with notes of honeydew and cantaloupe.
What's the name of it again?
Melon-cart.
Oh.
Not melon-colly, just melon-cart.
But that said, let me pour.
That was Peter taking a pee before he pours his beer.
Here's Peter drinking the pee.
[both laugh]
Ahh.
It's good. It's good.
You know, if you like watermelon beers, it's good.
Actually, you know, I take this back. This, now, today...
I think it has more flavor than the Guava Cart does.
Oh, you've got to talk about percentages and other...
I will.
...significant figures.
I will talk about significant figures.
This one is a whopping 4.0 alcohol.
Mhm.
4.0% 4% alcohol. So it's a light one. Yes, they could sell this in Costa Rica without having to go to prison
now
What I think is really cool though is that I've just noticed now looking at their website for the first time
They have a number more like when I saw my looked I don't think they only had a few but they've got
Another one called street cart. Yeah, I saw that which is lime and salt cerveza. They have
Spicy mango cart. They've got right on cart. I guess that one doesn't say cart. They have a non-alk
mango cart with no elk
But they also have they've got a blonde ale now
They've got Christmas cart. So I'm guessing that's gonna be like with spices and they have an Oktoberfest
So I have to try these
Because you know so far they're pretty good
They also have a bunch of IPAs, which I'm not impressed by.
It looks like they've got something for the Rams.
Although, correct me if I'm wrong,
what is that World Champions one for?
That's for the Rams, right?
That looks like a football field in the background
on that page for that one.
I'm not sure which one you're looking at.
World Champions, it's called Whose House?
Champion Champango?
Oh, Whose House? No, Whose House.
Okay, Whose House?
World Champions, and it's got what looks like a Rams logo.
And if you click on that beer,
it has a football field in the background.
So I'm guessing those are the Rams.
Did the Rams win something or apparently I don't know. I don't follow American.
It is by the less. Yes, it is a Los Angeles Rams tribute beer. Oh, okay.
Not to be confused with the Los Angeles Rams tribute band.
That's totally different.
I wish it was a Los Angeles Rams tribute beer in the sense of tribute to one who
has passed on because who the hell cares about American football, Peter. Anyway,
Rams. So yeah, they don't seem to have Mellon cart anymore, dear listener.
So I'm sorry you can't enjoy this unless you already have it. I guess.
I think spicy mango cart sounds pretty good. I think you should find yourself some of that.
I'm going to go look for it. Real mango and authentic spice with a deliciously subtle finish.
Wait, what time of year is it? Are we past Christmas or are we headed to Christmas? We're
past Christmas. You can't get the Christmas cart. We are past Christmas, right. But I don't know
about spicy mango cart. We'll find out. We'll find out. And I also can't get Oktoberfest for
a few months either. That's true, yeah. But anyway, that's it. Golden Road Brewing,
They do good stuff. I like their beer. How are we going to link to this?
I don't know. I'll have to, I might have to google. Golden Road Brewing. Watermelon.
Melon Cart. Oh, Melon Cart, not WaterMelon Cart. Melon Cart. Yeah, so you can find it on things
like beeradvocate.com. That's probably the best. Apparently this was Apparently Craft Shack is a
website. Okay, Craft Shack is a website. Apparently it's been around for a while though,
though, because I just found a review on beer advocate and it's like five years old. So
yeah, it's good to advocate for beer. Yeah, it's good. Ever even a beer needs an advocate.
Even a beer needs an advocate. Yeah. So I like it. I would drink this. I gotta say it.
The pictures on the beer advocate website are horrible. So here's what you can do. Set
it down on the table, set that can down on the table and take a nice picture of it with
your iPhone for me. I will use that as the image. I'll take it right in front of my Macintosh
I pushed it in my Mac.
Ooh, even better.
Bonus!
Well, actually, if I look on images on the web, there's a lot of them, but that's fine.
I want your image.
I want it with Peter's Macintosh-io.
Very good.
This is live iphoneography happening, dear listener.
You can't beat this.
You can't touch this.
Okay, photos have been taken, Scott.
Beautiful.
You're a good human being.
Hey, remember how last time, was it last time we talked when you had an oral care patient
downstairs?
Oral care patient.
Or was it the time before?
It might have been the time before.
Somebody had just had mouth surgery.
Hello.
Yes.
Now I know what you're talking about.
I was thinking about myself because like I, I've got a bit of a pain, like a, you know,
crown thing going on myself.
So I was like, what is he talking about?
I haven't seen the dentist.
Yes.
I did have someone who required oral care.
My wife is downstairs having just had gum surgery today and so now I feel like the roles
are reversed here.
We've come full circle.
She also is not allowed to have alcohol for some period of time.
There we go.
I told her obviously you're the beer drinker in this house, I said to her, so you'll have
to stop.
I mean, if she was desperate.
It was pretty funny though when she came out of there she was pretty out of it loopy because
of course they gave her sedatives.
And so she was trying to... they were asking her when she wanted to come back for a follow-up
And so she gave him a date and then she was tapping on that date on her iPhone calendar furiously and nothing was happening
And she just kept tapping it over and over and over and over and over and I was just standing there going are you in?
There and then finally she realized she needed to go up to the top and tapped a little plus sign and make the event
So she did that but it was it was enjoyable watching her
Careful you're being recorded right now. She
She, well, first of all, she doesn't listen to this, and secondly, she's had time to laugh at me because when I had,
I think it was my skin cancer surgery, when I had my skin cancer surgery and I had propofol,
and I was coming out of propofol, I was loopy.
I, they handed, they said, "Are you thirsty?" and I said, "Yep," and they said, "Here's some water," and they handed me a cup of water
and I said, "Thanks!" Whoosh, and dumped it right over the edge of the bed.
Just, no hesitation, no delay, just, "Thanks!" Whoosh.
Oh my god.
Oh, wait, how many beers had you had prior to that surgery?
I had had propofol, the best beer of all.
Oh my god, I know why Michael Jackson wanted to die at the hands of that stuff.
Are you going to review that for our next episode?
I would love to.
It is the best sleep you'll ever have.
You'll wake up happy, you'll, oh my god.
Thanks.
I'll drink to propofol.
And then the poor nurse was standing there looking at it and I'm just laughing hilariously.
I will drink to propofol. Oh my god. Yeah, at least I had trained professionals.
I have a topic, yes. And it does relate to smart homes and stuff.
There are no smart homes, Peter.
So for about a year and a half or so, I have been on an ecobee. I switched to them from
nest two Black Fridays ago. And in general it works. Some of the stuff though, I don't
know if I'm just doing it wrong or if they just do it differently. But one thing I used
to have with my nest was if I would leave, you know, and the geofence would trip, it
would just turn the heat way down, right? So like, I mean, turn the heat down in the
summertime it would just turn the AC off, right? So I would say go to Vermont for a
few days and you know, it would say like, yeah, well we're going to set the heat to
45 because there's no long, no reason to keep it any warmer than that. The reason I got
rid of the nest is it stopped reliably tracking the geofence. And then one day I was up in
Vermont during a cold snap for like three days and the heat was blasting here the entire
time because it never realized that I left and I got frankly, you know, very angry and
you know, rip the thing out of the wall and replace it with a new one. Okay, great. The
ecobee when I leave, it's like, Oh yeah, you're gone. We're going to take the temperature
and drop it from like 72 to 68. So it just drops it just a little bit, but it never really
goes to the away depth that I would expect it to. And I'm not sure why. I'm not sure
what I'm doing wrong with that. So that's one question.
I don't know, but one thing I will tell you is if you're trying to use it with both HomeKit
and use the Ecobee app and set up triggers inside Ecobee itself, you're going to meet
very limited success.
I'm not currently able to use it with HomeKit at all because the device is not registered.
No, that's different. We'll get to that. Just plain old Ecobee and its app.
Yeah, I have no idea. I don't use any of the ecobee functions. But I will tell you this, ecobee does tie into your local electric companies.
They can get messages about, "Hey, this is a time where you need to save energy."
And so, like, during a hot spell when everybody in the universe has their AC on, it might raise your temperature a bit automatically.
I've done that.
that. And then you'll just be in your house and all of a sudden you'll be going like you're
irrationally angry and then you look at your ecobee and you realize why. You're on energy saver mode
or whatever or it's pre-conditioning or something. It's been talking to the electric company and
they're like you know this guy looks way too comfortable. No no I'm not saying that's your
problem I'm not relating it to that at all I'm just saying it does things like that. That's the
only thing that I have where the ecobee is in control. Everything else any triggers any stuff
that I want to have change on a schedule, any stuff that I want to have change on a
geofence, it's all HomeKit.
Yes.
All HomeKit.
Well, hopefully with my new one, which I do now have sitting downstairs, I'll be able
to take advantage of these because hopefully it'll actually work.
So I guess what I'm saying is, I don't know.
I seem to remember though, there's a way for you to say in this mode, here's what the temperature
should be.
Like you should be able to set a temperature that you want it to drop to.
I'm assuming that you do have a temperature set that you want it to drop to when you're
a home and it never goes there. Is that what you're saying? Right. The comfort settings.
Comfort. If I go into it, I'm just curious. Let me go into it right now. My ecobee. More. Settings.
Comfort settings. Away. So right now, the away desired heat is set. So this would be default
because I had to reset this thing a while ago. Right now the default away is 64 degrees. I'm
I'm gonna crank that down.
I'm gonna make it like--
Oh, well then it's working.
I'm gonna make it like 50.
All right, I just made it 50.
And I'm gonna save that.
We'll see if that works next time.
Okay, so wait, I don't know.
Can you leave for a little bit?
Can you go-Now?
Yeah, you wanted to find out if this works?
Sure, but you were the one who said
you were on the time crunch,
so if you want to just monologue
for the last half of the show, why not?
Why not?
So we'll see what happens.
But anyway, after my long saga...
Yeah, talk about the saga, because it sounds to me like the latest in the steps in order
to resolve this did not work, which you were thinking it wasn't going to work.
Yes, did not work.
All right, so explain to dear listener, where did you talk about this?
Did you talk about this on Blurring the Lines?
Because I've heard this story before.
I know that you've said some of it to me already, but I think you guys...
Yeah, but didn't you guys talk about it on Blurring the Lines?
I think we did too.
I think we discussed it over there.
I don't recall at this point, but Google does.
You have no idea.
Anyway, after many, many, many, many hours
of troubleshooting, I was able to finally get my ecobee
to pair with HomeKit, but that's as far as it would go.
And like, it would pair it and it was like,
oh, you've got these sensors.
You have a kitchen door sensor
and you have an upstairs sensor
and you have a bedroom sensor.
Do you want to add all these?
I was like, yes.
What room do you want to add it?
Bedroom, kitchen, living room, dining room.
Yep, perfect, that's great.
Got it all, accessory is not responding.
And so, you know, I went through all kinds of troubleshooting
trying to use my phone as a hotspot, trying to,
they're like, oh, reboot your router, reboot your phone.
What do you mean use your phone as a hotspot?
Reboot your Eero.
I use my phone as a hotspot because they're telling me
it's gotta be something wrong with your internet provider,
your wireless.
So if you use your phone as a hotspot
to pair with HomeKit, you'll be fine. And so I tried that. And of course, it didn't
work. Later on, one of their techs said, "Well, no, they have to both be on the same wireless
network. They have to be on the same Wi-Fi." I'm like, "Well, my phone is generating Wi-Fi.
It's not on Wi-Fi when it's acting as a hotspot. So that's not going to happen." So they just
had me flailing. They had no idea what they were doing. And then finally, after I took
a break over, you know, in Costa Rica for a bit and come back. They said, Oh, we, and
I quote, "changed something on the back end, try again." And this time trying again, it
actually would pair. Normally it would just try and try and try. It's like unable, you
know, the accessory did not respond, cannot pair. Suddenly one day it just works. Now
I'm pretty sure to make that happen, I had to use my Verizon Fios routers wireless and
bypass the Eero altogether. But even then, once that was done, now that it's paired, it shows up.
I click on it in HomeKit, but it says no response. The accessory is not responding. And that's where
it's been stuck since it connected. So that's as far as it's gone. So they said, for all the
trouble they were having, they would ship me a new unit. And so they upgraded my Ecobee3 Lite to the
latest ecobee with the smart assistant. So it's a significant upgrade. That's the good news. The
bad news is it's physically a different form factor. So I have to rip the whole mounting
bracket out of the wall and rewire everything again. Which you did already, right? No, I haven't
done it yet. Oh, so you don't know if this will fix it. The last step might fix it. Okay. It might.
It might. I don't know yet. But can't you just let it hang off the wall for now? Can't you just like
Well, I still have to pull the old one out and undo all the wires and redo them and stuff.
The wiring is super easy.
Just let it hang there.
I know, but I've got other things to do.
I've got other things to do, and number two, the mounting bracket, like the screws where
it mounts into, they've been drilled into and out of so many times.
It's very weak and wimpy, and it doesn't hold very well.
So I have to have my electrician come back for another small project, and I'm going to
probably just have him mount a whole new little bracket in there and that way it'll be firm and safe and
I won't screw it up.
See, just to test if it actually made a difference, I would
personally, I would just connect the wires and let it hang there and see if it does anything.
Then once it does or doesn't, I have to undo it and put the old one back in and mount it back into place and
Yeah, but it's just taking three wires out of the back of an ecobee is not...
No, it's not. But mounting the damn thing back on so it stays in the wall is.
And that's why I don't want to do it.
But what I'm saying is if it doesn't make a difference,
are you going to keep the new one anyway?
Yeah, why not?
Because apparently-
Supposedly it'll work withwell, supposedly it'll work with, um, it'll be a smart speaker.
So I can get rid of an A-word, or I can, if it works with HomeKit, I have Siri there.
So, yeah.
Or I could turn around and sell it.
it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Keep the old one. But one other thing. So I have the,
I have the little remote sensors, the smart sensors. I forget it comes with
little sensors, right? So I've got one upstairs here in my room in my,
at my third floor room and I have one in the, uh, in the bedroom and they
participate, right? So you can say this room will participate in your home
setting or your sleep setting. Right. Last night, and again today, I'm downstairs, or
I was up here today and I'm like sweltering. It is so freaking hot and I don't know what's
going on. I look at the, you know, the like heat is just blasting out of this thing. Full
back full, full bore. I look at the ecobee and it's like, yeah, the temperature in this
room is 76 and we're just pumping more heat into it. And I was like, yeah, but I only
want it to be 71. Well, it was super hot in the room that I was in, but it was cold in another room
where I wasn't. Now, I thought that if I left and I wasn't in that room,
and it didn't detect motion, that it would say, "There's nobody here."
I don't think that's how it works. I think it just tries to balance the sensors.
It just tries to balance all the heat and that does not happen very well in a three-story townhouse.
No it doesn't.
And it knows that it's a three-story townhouse because it asked me during setup,
"What type of home do you have? Is it an apartment? Is it a condo?"
It's a townhouse. So that's a little frustrating.
But I also have it integrated with my Flair smart vents, which I still haven't exactly figured out.
So the ecobee itself is in the living room and I also have vents in the living room.
And it seems like if I change the temperature on the ecobee, the living room temperature that the
flare vents are set to tracks that. Sometimes vice versa. Because there's a separate app for the
vents and you can set the temperature there. All it does with the vent though is it controls whether
it's open or closed. So it's like, oh, it's cold in the living room, let's open the vents and let the
heat out, right? But there have definitely been conditions where they're not getting along,
and like it's cold in the living room, but and it's calling for more heat, but the flare has
been set to close. The vents closed, yeah. Yeah, so honestly, because of these stupid, you know,
these heat sensors, I'm wondering like, should I just get rid of them? Because they're not really
helping and I'm not really clear too. I didn't even double check if the flares themselves have
temperature sensors on them as well if the vents do because sometimes it will be showing like,
"Oh yeah, the temperature is 72 degrees," but I looked at the ecobee sensor and it's like,
"No, it's 76." So they seem to have their own idea as to where the temperature comes.
So I don't know. It's been frustrating, but I've found that I seem to have the best results
just doing it manually. I say open the vents on the third floor or close the vents on the third
floor and turn up the heater turn down the heat and I seem happier with that. Yeah this is why
I don't know anything about those flares but I'm guessing they will never be on HomeKit.
Probably not. They're there well I mean they're about they cost about 90 bucks a piece.
Doesn't mean anything so well there you can sometimes yeah
Yeah, I don't think that they're they would say if they were homekit compatible
Yeah, I I was not into that at the time when I bought them
So I don't remember but I do have all of their boxes downstairs so I could find out
I know they're not there's no homekit. There's no
Yeah
So you know overall though I do like them they work pretty well
I don't like the fact that they are Zigbee, but they require you to buy their proprietary controller, Puck, as well.
They won't work with just another controller.
"Works with Ecobee and your room sensors too."
"Your room sensors know what rooms run hot or cold. With Flare, you can finally fix that."
Now here's the thing. What I don't know is what'll happen when your Ecobee is on HomeKit.
It's still using the sensors though, even if it's on HomeKit, so in theory it should still work.
It should. What it should do is it should make it so that you don't have to worry about your event, but obviously
You're saying that's not your experience so far. It's not really working. Yeah, I think honestly
I think I have more problems with the ecobee sensors. So all I did is I just took all of the sensors out
I'm like don't participate in any of these settings
Which makes me wonder why do I even have the sensors? I don't know. So anyway
Such is life first world problems my friend first world problems. I'm gonna drink more beer. How about you?
I am too, but there's not a whole lot more to drink. There's this much left
I also have not a whole lot more to drink, but let's let's fix that
Let's make it so we have no more to drink your beer. Just got all fuzzy it is
Cheers, cheers
So that's ecobee versus flare. What else is going on heard about any good bank collapses lately
No, but I will say this I saw some
screenshots of Jason Calacanis's tweets.
[laughter]
His all-caps tweets telling the government to get their ass in gear and save everybody.
Right.
Grab your guns.
Who's with me?
These a$$----s, these guys, they do not want the government to ever be involved in anything.
They want them to stay out of their way.
These guys are basically techno-libertarians until they need help.
And then all of a sudden they want to be part of society.
And it just pisses me off.
guys are so bad for society, they're so bad for the world, they're so bad for the world of technology.
This is why when we were talking about Mosaic I was thinking about Egghead. What's his name? The
guy with the big round oval head? Andresen. Andresen. Mark Andresen. No, I'm serious,
he's got, he looks like an alien skit from Saturn Hat Life. He's definitely been moving in that
direction, yes. Yeah, and so he is another one that is just bad for society. He's just an a**hole.
He's just a flat-out a**hole.
Yep, a lot of popping sounds.
Even more.
It just kills me when people don't want to participate in society. They want to color outside the lines.
They want to do their own thing. They want to reap the benefits and not share with anyone else.
But then when it comes time for them to suffer, they don't want to. They want someone to come bail them out.
And they're so transparent about it. Like they don't even care who sees what they are doing.
Mm-hmm. Well, they think they're above the law. Do they care at all? Apparently not.
I know the answer is no, but I can't I don't know how you get to become that kind of person.
Narcissism? Probably, I guess. They are the main character.
You seem to be enjoying that. I am. I am. I'm more than I expected to. I've actually-
I'm getting to like, you know, like less strong, I won't say weak, but I guess relatively speaking,
weaker beers and I'm okay with them. They do have a benefit. I like being able to drink them and not
feel anything like, yeah, I don't get plastered. I mean, I feel something. Yeah, but you can have
one beer and it's not going to wreck your day. And like a couple hours later you could even do
a workout if you wanted to. A couple hours, sure. Today's a rest day for me though. Yeah, but, but
But what I mean is if you drink a 9%er,
you're probably not gonna feel good during a workout later,
even if you wait three hours or so.
Probably not gonna work out the next day with a 9%.
I'm serious, those things like knock me down.
Whoo, ah boy, I tell ya.
Yeah, so that was fun.
Yeah, Silicon Valley Bank did not directly affect me yet,
but we'll probably all feel it in the form of-
Hey, you just made me curious. Why would it affect you?
Well, maybe I invested in firms there or maybe I own shares of Silicon Valley Bank.
You would know when you, and if you don't know,
it would be so diluted that it shouldn't matter that much.
No, I know it did not affect me directly. I just said that. I know it did not affect me.
Right. But you said something to the effect.
It will affect everybody indirectly.
Maybe because we're going to have greater regulation coming down the road and
And that's going to require what's going to cost more.
Interest rates are going to have to be higher because banks are going to have to absorb
more money.
So, oh my God, they're making so much money.
The banks don't have to absorb money.
They will.
They don't have to, but they will.
Yeah.
The banks, they're not suffering.
I can't join the bank pity party here.
Pity party bank.
So anyway, so I've got a marathon coming up.
Yeah.
it when that was? About three weeks. Are you on schedule? I am. I'm a little concerned.
This schedule is... it really seems really light. I'm just afraid. I don't know if...
I'm not sure if I feel... Well, that's what I was wondering. That's why I was asking,
because when I look at... I don't check all your workout notifications, but most of the
ones I check, it doesn't look like you're putting in as much distance yet as I thought
you would be? I'm not, yeah, but I'm on track with according to the schedule so
we'll see I just don't know I can't vouch for the efficacy of the schedule so. Who
wrote this schedule? Mark Andreessen. Mark Cuckoozella. It was a Mark! Does he have a big
egg-shaped head? A cuckoo mark. He's a cuckoo bird. He does not he does not have
an egg-shaped head so yeah well then what can you possibly know about
marathons Peter I know I mean geez with his tiny little cranium how smart can he
be okay remind me which marathon this is this is the cheap marathon in Derry
Hampshire cheap marathon are you serious that's the name of it oh my god it is
Mm-hmm. Ah, that is so awesome. The cheap marathon. The cheap marathon. Yep. Oh my god. The cheap marathon.
It's on millenniumrunning.com, is that right? Or is millenniumrunning.com just some random... oh, okay.
That's the company that puts it on, yeah. Oh my god, that's hilarious. The cheap marathon.
You know what that means, they're gonna take terrible pictures of you. Are they gonna take any?
Who knows? Oh man.
It'll take a picture of you with some 20 year old android phone and it'll just capture your feet.
Maybe your shin. That's pretty cool.
Yeah, so that'll be fun.
Yeah, that looks like fun. It looks like a neat course.
It looks like you're running through the woods partially.
Yeah, it's a it's an old rail trail, you know, rails to trails.
Oh nice.
Yeah.
And I got a, um, I got a, uh, words, words.
The Words. They hard. I got an Airbnb a nine minute walk away from the start of the race.
Oh, so does the end go back around to the start? I would assume it does. Yes. Okay. Yes. So,
but after running a marathon, are you going to be able to walk for nine minutes?
I think I can handle nine more minutes. Yeah. Especially at the rate this one,
this is going. So yeah, I don't, you're going to eat so many M&Ms. You're going to be sick.
You're going to get to the finish line. You're going to fall over and puke. In which case,
if you do fall over they'll get your picture because before they were just taking your feet remember
Yeah, but you said there won't be a good picture. So it'll be no it won't be a good picture
Even if they took it even if it was a beautiful picture
It still won't be good because it'll be you laying on the ground puking mms
and then
And then you're gonna have to get up
Pretend like it didn't happen and run, you know
Then you could just be a forest gump and just run straight to the thing. That's nine minutes away run forest run
Oh, man, it'll be great. That's cool. No, that's a good idea
are all two of your, it was two other guys that are doing this with you, right?
One gal, one guy. Yeah. And the gal, Carola, she is like way more prepared, I think. And she,
like the other, like last week I ran like 10 miles and she ran like 18. And I'm like, yeah,
that's more like what I expected to be doing. But again, given the injury that I'm coming back from,
I think moderation is probably okay. So I'm still running a freaking marathon.
How is your body right now? Are you still wearing a brace and all that stuff?
I wore one yesterday. I did not wear one the day before for my one-hour jog
So yeah, it's it's more proactive stuff. But yeah, that's good. I'm more and more or less put back together
So yeah, things are things are looking good. So knock on wood. I
Just hope that after this one, you don't have any more stress fractures. What shoes you're gonna wear. I
Just ordered my first new pair of running shoes in like a year or so
So I ordered a pair of the Altra Escalante Racers.
They should be here day after tomorrow.
I have been running in the Altra Escalante 2.5s, which my running buddy Carola describes
as, and I quote her, "slow shoes."
So I'm hoping that by upgrading to the Racers that I'll gain a little speed.
Okay, these definitely have more cushion.
These actually look pretty good.
I like these.
I'm thinking that what I really want is something slightly thicker than my Merrell Vapor Glows.
Okay, so yeah, well, that's not hard to do.
Right, that's what I mean.
They're so minimal, there's almost nothing there.
So the Ultra-Eraser is fairly minimal, but it is not a minimalist shoe.
It is a zero-drop shoe, but it's not a minimalist shoe.
And that might be enough for me.
Zero-drop might be all I really need.
Now I have had a lot of fun though running in my zero speed forces again
Oh got those out two or three times this past week
Those are like super minimalists. They're like even thinner than the vapor gloves
Oh, I don't know if I want that then yeah, but they feel really good and I was pretty fast with them
So but I would not move in that direction. One thing I will say though is they do
seem to provide
Not more support
But they provide more protection against like rocks and pebbles and stuff than the vapor gloves do yeah
Yeah, yeah, the vapor gloves have nothing. Yeah, so that's my plan there and then
Let's see. I'm curious you are I wanted to ask you about this. You are an Apple TV plus subscriber, correct?
That is correct. Hey, no, wait, do you just do Apple one? Yeah, you do the whole thing. Yeah, you're full
Okay, so you get news you get TV you get health or workouts?
Fitness fitness plus right? Yeah, you know, okay. I almost never look at this stupid news up though
Well, I have like three months of the free, you know of the news app and I just I haven't touched it
I haven't really done anything with it. It's a downer. It's not something you should read it. Look at if you want your mouth intact
Yeah, well, that's a I haven't been so I'm like great. I've got this free for three months and so far
I like I used it once and I was like, yeah, this is why I don't do that. Yeah
Yeah, this is why I don't do that.
Anyway.
But Apple TV+, are you watching Ted Lasso?
I did.
So far, there's only been one new episode, but I did watch it.
Okay.
I'm not there yet.
So I have not resubscribed.
I'd call you a big dummy poo-poo face if you didn't.
You're a big dummy poo-poo face if you don't, Peter.
So I have not yet resubscribed to watch Ted Lasso or any others.
I've been hearing good things, though.
I've been hearing in my echo chamber more good things about Apple TV Plus, and it's
the cheapest out of all the services, Netflix, HBO, Disney, or whatnot.
They have a lot of good shows on there right now.
That's what I'm hearing.
The other one that I've been watching is called Shrinking with...
I heard good things about that.
Yeah, a different Jason.
Yep.
Not Jason Calacanis, either of those.
Not Calacanis.
No, no, no.
I wouldn't watch a show about him.
not all caps tweeting the government to bail them out. Although I am watching Silicon Valley again,
which has a Jason Calacanis-like character in it. Isn't that on HBO? Yeah. See, I don't want to
watch that because why would I watch that? It's just too close to reality. It's just...
It is, and it's freaking hilarious. That's why. That's why you would watch it. It is hilarious.
It is so well done. Almost every single episode is just like, it's just one step away from
absolute reality, but it's also hilarious.
Yeah, I just, I hate modern Silicon Valley so bad. Silicon Valley is a pox on society right now.
It's a cancer.
It definitely could be doing more harm than good, but I don't know. Some days. To some people,
it's definitely doing more harm than good.
And it's not even silicon. There's nothing silicon about it. It's venture capitalists
and people writing software. It has nothing... What people call Silicon Valley now, it has nothing to
do with Silicon Valley. And the actual places where they make silicon aren't in San Francisco.
Not anymore.
Oh boy.
No, they never were. They were always in San Jose, in Santa Clara, and the other Sans,
but not the San Francisco.
San Jose.
I doubt that you could put a fav in San Francisco. So, uh, you should get Apple TV. You could get
Apple TV Plus. I could. You could watch Ted Lasso. I want you to because I want to know
what you think of it. I will, but I'll probably wait. I'll probably wait a month or so.
How many episodes are going to be in this final season? I don't know. Well, all right. I am
watching The Mandalorian. I did just finish watching The Last of Us. How is The Mandalorian?
because I've only watched part of one episode. But then my wife was watching it the other day,
and I looked over and I saw that he was back on, is it Tatooine where that lady who fixes his ship
is always... And I just saw her again and I'm like, they're just doing the same old hits over
and over again. Is it better than that? >> They definitely have a lot of repeats.
Oh, it's definitely better than that too. No, yeah. No, they're bringing a lot of recurring
characters in, but that's not a bad thing. >> It's not just 100% fan service and no...
No, not 100. There's a lot of fan service and apparently I had no way of I did not
know this. I'm not that much of a Star Wars geek. But apparently, like every scene has
some kind of Easter eggs that if you watched all the shows, read the books, read the comics,
played the games, etc. There's tons of fan service payoffs that I don't know. And you
when I was a kid, I loved Star Wars. I was never super all into Star Wars, though.
Yeah, you didn't read all the third party books and all that other horse poop.
No. I don't think I even ever bought one because Dark Horse Comics used to publish the Star Wars
comics. I don't think I ever even bought a single one of those. I had a bunch of the toys, but then
shortly thereafter, I found out about G.I. Joe and I promptly migrated. And, you know, so that's
where I was. But you know, I saw all the movies. I enjoyed them. Well, okay, the last two, pretty
lame. But you know, I liked them. But out of all of those things, as far as cinematics or TV goes
and stuff, I still think Mandalorian is the best of all of those. I think that, uh, oh my god,
what was it called? The one where, the one where they went to get the Death Star plans. Rogue One.
Yeah, I thought that was the best. That was my favorite Star Wars movie of all.
It was good. I liked The Mandalorian better.
Yeah.
Yep.
I guess the problem with The Mandalorian is it has the normal problem of TV, which is TV budgets
are inherently going to be smaller. And so if you have something go on for long enough, you can see
where they did spend the budget and where they didn't spend the budget. And that leaves a very
uneven taste that I'm not a giant fan of.
But then again, if you watch the movies that came out in the late 90s and early 2000s or the ones
that came out in the late teens versus the ones that came out in 1977, you can also see an absence
of budget and an absence of special effects capabilities. Right, but at least the early
movies are consistent within themselves. Fair, yes. Yeah, I get that. There have been a couple
of episodes where it didn't feel to me like they were skimping on budget as much as just like
they just the director the direction was lacking a little bit i was like you really could have done
better than this yeah they're just like oh let's go home pretty much but that doesn't but you're
right that does not happen very often in mandalorian it's pretty good and i and i don't
know what their budget is but whatever resources they have they seem to do a pretty amazing job
with him. Yep. Yeah. No, I'm enjoying it. I like it. It beats the hell out of the Boba Fett one.
Oh, you mean Mandalorian season 2.5? Yeah. Boba Fett was just sad. It was just sad. It's like,
I don't know why people liked Boba Fett to begin with, but whatever, whoever liked him
can't like him anymore because like they just lame-o'd him out of existence. No, they did lame-o
Boba Fett. I don't know what the hell they were thinking there. He definitely got lame-o'd.
They took this guy who was supposed to be a badass bounty hunter and they turned him into a guy who
just wants to sit on a throne and have people pay homage to him. I'm like, "What? Are you kidding me?"
Yeah, but he wants to do so diplomatically and be a nice guy though. He's not just sitting there
like a hut. He's like, "Oh, there's problems. Well, let's go out and see what we can do. Let's
go." And, "Oh, well, we shouldn't just kill this guy. Let's hear him out." All of a sudden,
he's a nice guy. I was like, "What the hell happened?" Anyway. But in addition to that,
though. Speaking of Pedro Pascal, I also finished watching The Last of Us. Well, yes, The Hot Wings
also. I saw that too. That was entertaining. But The Last of Us was even better than The Last of
the Hot Wings. They should have named that episode The Last of Us Hot Wings. The Last of Us. That
would be pretty funny. So I watched the whole first season of The Last of Us, which is the
only season right now. I don't think that's an HBO thing, right? Yes, it is. Yeah, it was good.
It was good. I did like it. It's definitely a new twist on post-apocalyptic zombie movie or series.
Was it written by Chad Chibitie?
It was not. It's not as gross as, say, The Walking Dead. Not as much gratuitous gore.
What was your preacher's name?
Jeremiah Strong. But no, I liked The Last of Us. So, minor spoiler alert, which they pretty much
give away in the first scene. The premise is that mushrooms evolve to take over humans.
Okay. Anybody who's done mushrooms could probably see where that came from.
Well, I do this mushroom every day. This is the funny part. I regularly take Cordyceps
militaris for increased focus and energy. And the funny thing is, the precept for this movie
is that Cordyceps militaris evolves to a point where it can survive in human beings.
Oh, so this is literally the exact mushroom that you're...
It is literally... If I had my bottle, I would hold up the label and show you it is the exact
mushroom that I eat. Oh my god, there's a website called mushroomrevival.com. I'm not kidding.
And that's where I buy mine from. That's where I get mine from. Now, mushroom revival is where I
get some. If you're interested in, I'll send you a referral code. Highly recommended. Anyway,
I definitely liked The Last of Us.
It got a little extreme, you know,
a little bit graphic at times,
but I overall enjoyed it.
So it was pretty good.
I installed a browser.
Is it a browser extension?
It is a browser extension.
I installed a browser extension called the Magic Highlighter.
The Magic Highlighter.
But here's the thing.
So like if you do a normal search on a website, right?
Just do a normal search in the search bar
or the search/URL bar.
whatever terms you search for,
it will highlight those terms on the page
that you go to from the search results.
Oh, that's nice.
Can't decide if I like it or not because it doesn't,
it always defaults to yellow.
And if I want a different color,
I have to do the Command + Shift + F
to bring up that extensions pop-up,
and then I can select a different color.
I don't want to do that.
I want to...
Is this a Safari extension?
Yeah, it's in the Mac App Store, I just said.
I just said.
Sorry, I missed that part.
I've had a beer.
Back off.
No, you haven't.
You've had a 4%.
That's not a beer.
That's a beer.
It's a weak beer, but it's a beer.
Yeah, so anyway, I can't decide if I like it
'cause it's kind of cool that all the,
so you type in some search terms,
you click on one of the results,
and then on that page it highlights all the terms
that you searched for.
Okay.
But like I said, I want to be able to pick a color
and have it stick to that color from then on
instead of having it always pop up in yellow
'cause I just hate the yellow highlighting.
The other thing too is when it highlights some phrases on a webpage,
you can do Command-Shift-F to open the options for the Magic Highlighter,
and you can unclick, or you can click on one of the terms to make it go away
so that it's only highlighting specific terms that you want.
But I don't want that.
I would like a way to be able--
I would like something that you can click on that says,
"Stop highlighting any of them."
Hmm. Okay.
Because I want to do that sometimes,
but most of the time I just find it bloody distracting.
Like most of the time when I do search terms,
I don't want those specific words on the page.
I want the article.
I want the information about the topic
and not where on the page are those specific words.
So sometimes it is super handy, but a lot of times it's not.
And so I haven't decided what I'm going to do with this.
But anyway, there it is.
Use it as you will.
It sounds cool.
I generally try to install as few extensions in my browser as I can.
So I'm not sure if I think it sounds cool enough for me to actually install it.
I don't even know what I, I think I have 1Password installed in Safari.
That might be the only extension I have.
Yeah, I've got 1Password.
I've got 1Blocker, which is good.
I've got save to good links, which I like to be able to save stuff to good links.
I've got homecoming for Mastodon, which allows you to open Mastodon
URLs in your own instance.
So like if you get someone's Mastodon URL or something,
you can use this to automatically go to your instance
and then you can follow that person or something like that.
Yep.
I've got a, believe it or not,
I've got a kaleidoscope dev tool thing in there,
which will diff web pages for me.
It's a full featured app,
but it also has a Safari thing so that I can diff web pages,
which comes in nice when you're doing development work,
for example.
So I have the Magic Highlighter, I've got Subscribe to Feed so that I can dump websites right into
NetNewswire, which is what I use for my RSS.
I've got Noir, which allows you to, for websites that don't have a dark mode,
if you're in dark mode, it will, if you're in dark mode on the Mac, it will make the webpage dark for you
so that you're not blasted in the middle.
How is that?
It's okay. It's not bad.
The good news is, first of all, you can set custom themes so you can decide how the dark
web page is going to look, but you can also do...
Oh, what are the shortcuts?
Oh my God.
Apparently there is a competing browser extension called turnoffthelights.com.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's several of these.
And they are bad mouthing the Noir extension.
Yeah, I don't...
I don't...
Anybody that bad mouth somebody else, I automatically am prejudiced against the person doing the
bad mouth.
It's not a good look.
Anyway, there's a keyboard shortcut for Noir that you can do and so you can toggle through
auto, off, or on.
So if you go to a website and for some reason it's screwing up the legibility you can just
real quick do a keyboard shortcut to turn it off for that site and so then your webpage
is legible again.
That's one thing I do like about it.
I have a plugin for Raindrop which is what I keep all my bookmarks in.
Raindrop.io.
And then I've got a couple for cleaning stuff up like Super Agent for Safari which fills
out cookies so you never get the cookie pop-ups and vinegar which replaces the
YouTube player with a minimal HTML player and it also hmm does vinegar
block YouTube ads I don't think it does but something I have installed does
block YouTube ads I think it's the it might be 1Blocker that I'm using that
blocks the YouTube ads anyway I've got something that blocks YouTube ads so
when it when a YouTube video is playing it just skips right over the ads for me
Okay, well there you go. Yeah, so I have a few, I have a few, but they're all useful.
They're all good stuff. Cool. I definitely don't install, I certainly wouldn't just
install random stuff from the Chrome extension store, no. And I'm pretty
careful about installing extensions in who I hear about them from or are they
already part of apps that I already use and trust? I don't. Like 1Password for instance.
Like 1Password good links, you know people that I know who those people are net news wire guy Brent Simmons
He's written a lot of stuff. In fact, he he's written several of the scripts that I use
He's is he wrote the bunch app that I use. He's got a lot of good Mac
Automation tools so no good. So there you go. I don't know how we got down that rabbit hole
I don't either but I think that's about all I have at the moment
Yeah, I think it's all I have to by the way in the time we've been podcasting. It's gone from
um, looking like a sunny, cheerful morning in your apartment, in your condo, in your
townhouse.
Sorry, I got it wrong.
I want to make sure that I match what you told EkoB.
It's gone from that to looking like you're about to hold some kind of black magic ceremony.
Well that's because the sun went down.
Is Alistair Crawley coming over to your house right now?
Probably.
The house, the house, the house did go down.
Peter, your house went down.
The house just went down.
The sun did go down really rapidly because it pretty much went down while I was looking
at my Safari extensions. It was that fast. Yeah, well, the sun did go down and, you know,
it happens quick around here, but luckily I can say things like, "Hey Siri, turn on
all the lights." And now lights turn on. Amazing. The one thing about HomeKit that bothers me,
and I know that this is a hard problem to solve, but it's the variability with timing.
Sometimes I'll say turn on my bedroom lamp or whatever and bam, it is on. And other times
I've already stumbled around the dark, tripped over some things and made it to the side of
my bed by the time it turns on the bloody lamp.
Mine tends to be more on the trip over the side of the bed stumbling timeframe.
And that's one place where I'll definitely tell you that A-word, the lady in the tube
from our friends from Bezos and other world domination.
From Spy World Incorporated.
They have that beat like no one's business.
So I definitely like there'll be times when I'll be waiting for Apple.
And while I'm waiting, I'll just tell the lady in the tube to do it.
And she does it before Apple is just like, "Sorry, something went wrong."
Let's put it this way.
Jeff Bezos already knows what lights you're turning on and where you are in your house
before Siri can even process your command.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, he definitely does.
Yeah, no question.
He's definitely concerned about that.
He doesn't have anything else on his mind.
So if people want to get ahold of us...
I have no idea.
Do they know how to?
Well, I'll be downstairs in just a minute, checking on my wife.
So if you need to get ahold of us, you can go downstairs and check on Scott and his wife.
Go downstairs to my house, yeah.
Yes, perfect.
FriendsWithBrews.com.
It has all of the episodes.
It has more transcripts every day, Peter.
In fact, I just finished transcribing episode two, although I haven't quite posted that yet.
And it has all the brews. It has a wonderful search feature so that you can search for
things that we've drunk or things that have made us drunk. And it also has the friends page,
I think it's called, and that gives links to our websites and our Mastodon,
or elephant-sized instances that we're part of.
No? Too soon?
Elephant-sized instances.
Oh boy.
Yeah, I got nothing.
You have a big red button.
I'm gonna push it.